selz.com 2018-09-19

# Privacy Policy - Selz

## Introduction

This Privacy Policy explains what information Selz Pty Ltd., a company registered in Australia (ABN 29 163 769 837) and its related entities ("Selz") collect about you and why, and what we do with that information. It also explains the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information, whether you are a merchant or end user that uses Selz products, applications or services (together, the “Services”), a buyer that shops at a store using our technology, or whether you are simply visiting a website owned and operated by Selz. 

By using any Selz Services, or by dealing with a merchant using Selz services you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and, as applicable, the Selz Terms of Service. 

## Information relating to our Merchants

  1. What information do we collect from Merchants?

We collect information that is required to enable us to manage your account, for identification and authentication purposes, service improvement, to provide our Services including support services, to address malicious use of our Services and for legal and regulatory purposes.

Specifically, we collect:

    1. At account creation: we collect your name, company name, address, email address and phone number and other information you may provide us about your business. We use this information to provide you with our Services. We also collect this information to make sure we comply with legal requirements.
    2. At plan subscription: we collect your payment/billing information, for example, credit card information. We use this information to collect payment from you for using our Services.
    3. At Selz Pay application: we collect your business name, business ID, business directors, date of birth, bank account information, and government-issued identification information, such as your Social Security Number or a copy of your government-issued identification. We use this information to provide you with Selz Pay services, including fraud and risk monitoring, and to comply with legal and regulatory requirements.
    4. Usage Data: we also collect data about how and when you access your account and the Selz platform, including information about the browser you use, your network connection, your IP address and information about how you browse the Selz interface. We use this information to give you access and to improve our Services. We also use this information to provide you with advertising or marketing information. 
  2. How is this information collected?

We collect this information when you sign up for our Services, when you access our Services or otherwise provide us with the information. We may also collect personal information from third parties, such as our service providers, business affiliates and credit reporting agencies.

  3. How is this information shared?

Selz works with a variety of third parties and service providers to help provide you with our Services and we may share personal information with them to support these efforts. We may also share your information in the following circumstances:

    * To prevent, investigate, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations of our Terms of Service, or any other agreements related to the Services, or as required by law.
    * To help us conduct marketing and/or advertising campaigns.
    * To conform to legal requirements, or to respond to lawful court orders, subpoenas, warrants, or other requests by public authorities.
    * Personal information may also be shared with another company if it acquires our business, whether through merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, or other similar transaction or proceeding. If this happens, we will take appropriate steps to inform you, including sending you an email, if we have your email address, and posting notices on our home page.
    * Selz will always ask for your consent before sharing your personal information with third parties for purposes other than those described in Section: Third Party Apps.

## Information relating to our Buyers

  1. What information do we collect from Buyers?

    1. Usage data: we collect information about orders that Buyers initiate, information about the Selz-supported stores that Buyers visit, and information about the device and browser they use. We use this information to provide our Merchants with the Services, including supporting and processing orders and to improve our Services.
    2. Checkout data: we collect our Buyers’ name, email, shipping address, billing address, phone number, IP address, and any other custom fields as defined by our Merchants.

We use this information to provide our Merchants with the Services, including supporting and processing orders and for risk and fraud screening, and authentication.

  2. How is this information collected?

We collect this information when a Buyer uses or accesses an online store or online checkout that uses our Services, such as when a Buyer visits a Merchant’s site, or places an order on a Merchant’s site. We may also collect personal information from third parties, such as our service providers, and business affiliates.

  3. How is this information shared?

Selz works with a variety of third parties and service providers to help provide you with our Services and we may share personal information with them to support these efforts. We may also share your information in the following circumstances:

    * To prevent, investigate, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations of our Terms of Service, or any other agreements related to the Services, or as required by law.
    * If the Merchant whose store you visit or whose checkout you access directs us to transfer this information.
    * To conform to legal requirements, or to respond to lawful court orders, subpoenas, warrants, or other requests by public authorities.
    * Personal information may also be shared with another company if it acquires our business, whether through merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, or other similar transaction or proceeding. If this happens, we will take appropriate steps to inform you, including sending you an email, if we have your email address, and posting notices on our home page.

## Information relating to Selz website visitors and support users

  1. What information do we collect from website visitors and support users?

    1. Website visitors: we collect information about the device and browser visitors use, as well as the visitors’ network connection, IP address and information about the cookies installed on your device.
    2. Chat support: we collect chat support users’ name, email address, information about the device and browser you use, your network connection, IP address, chat transcript and other personal information you provide during the chat.

We use this information to verify your account, to provide and enhance our Services and answer any questions you may have.

  2. How is this information collected?

We collect this information from visitors and support users who visit the Selz website, use Services offered on our website or engage with us either by email, web form, or instant message.

  3. How is this information shared?

Selz works with a variety of third parties and service providers to help provide you with our Services and we may share personal information with them to support these efforts.

## Cookies and related tracking methods

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, we use cookies to store and sometimes track information about your use of this site (such as your preferences, session information and information on how you visit and access our web pages). A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your Internet web browser from our web server and stored on your computer, but does not contain any of your personal information. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can set your browser so that your computer does not accept them. We may also log IP addresses (the electronic addresses of computers connected to the Internet) to analyze trends, administer this site, track user movements on this site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use by us and our advertisers and business partners.

We also use cookies to serve targeted ads from Google, Facebook, Bing, and other third-party vendors.

Any user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If the User does this some parts of the Site may not function properly or be accessible.

## Third Party apps

Selz’s platform allows merchants to connect their stores with third party applications to alter or provide new functionalities in their store. Selz is not responsible for and has no control over how these apps function. Merchants ultimately can control which apps they choose to use with their stores, and are responsible for making sure that they do so in compliance with relevant privacy and data protection requirements.

## Account closure and your personal data

In general, we will continue to store archived copies of your personal information for legitimate business purposes and to comply with the law, except when we receive a valid erasure request or, if you are a merchant, you terminate your account and your information is purged pursuant to our standard process.

We will continue to store anonymous or anonymized information, such as website visits, without identifiers, in order to improve our Services.

## How we store and secure your personal information

We follow industry standards on information security management to safeguard sensitive information, such as financial information, intellectual property, employee details and any other personal information entrusted to us. Our information security systems apply to people, processes and information technology systems on a risk management basis.

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your personal information.

## Residents of the European Economic Area

Selz works with merchants and users around the world, including in the EEA. If you are located in the EEA, as part of our service, we may transfer your personal information to other regions, including to Australia, the United States and. In order to ensure that your information is protected when transferred out of the EEA, Selz relies on standard contractual data protection clauses, which have been approved by the European Commission.

If you are located in the EEA, you have certain rights under European law with respect to your personal data, including the right to request access to, correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your personal data. If you are a merchant, a partner, a visitor of Selz’s websites, or a user of Selz’s support services and wish to exercise these rights, please reach out to us using the contact information below. If you are a buyer and wish to exercise these rights, please contact the merchants you interacted with directly -- we serve as a processor on their behalf, and can only forward your request to them to allow them to respond.

Additionally, if you are located in the EEA, we note that we are generally processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above, unless we are required by law to obtain your consent for a particular processing operation.

If you have unresolved concerns, you may have the right to complain to a data protection authority in the country where you live, where you work or where you feel your rights were infringed.

## How we transfer information we collect internationally

We collect information globally and primarily store that information in the United States. We transfer, process and store your information outside of your country of residence, to wherever we or our third-party service providers operate for the purpose of providing you the Services. Whenever we transfer your information, we take steps to protect it, however these countries may not have equivalent privacy and data protection laws to the laws of many of the countries where our customers and users are based.

When we share information about you within and among Selz affiliates, we make use of standard contractual data protection clauses, which have been approved by the European Commission.

## Our policy towards children

The Services are not directed to individuals under 16. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 16. If we become aware that a child under 16 has provided us with personal information, we will take steps to delete such information. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information, please contact our support services.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice by adding a notice on the Services homepages, login screens, or by sending you an email notification. We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review. We encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you use the Services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

If you disagree with any changes to this privacy policy, you will need to stop using the Services and deactivate your account(s), as outlined above.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or feel that we are not abiding by the terms of this Privacy Policy, please contact our Data Protection Officer in any of the following ways:

By email at [privacy@selz.com](mailto:privacy@selz.com)

or

By post at:

Selz Pty Ltd.  
Attn: Data Protection Officer  
Suite 1D, Level 23  
1 Farrer Place  
Sydney NSW 2000  
AUSTRALIA
